francescascollections.com 2016-10-15

# Privacy and Security | francesca's

Revision Date: January 8, 2014

Thank you for shopping at francesca's® online boutique. francesca's® is committed to respecting the privacy rights and protecting the personal information of online visitors to our website.

### Personal Information We May Collect

While visiting the francesca's® online boutique, we may ask you to register and/or provide information that identifies you, including but not limited to your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, birth date, credit card or payment information, or other personal information. 

As a part of francesca's® ongoing efforts to provide you with an enjoyable and efficient shopping experience, we may use the personal information you choose to provide to us to personalize your shopping experience on this website. This information will also enable us to process, track and fulfill your order and to provide you with information we believe may be of interest to you.

Unless required by law, or circumstance as described below, francesca's® does not disclose any personal information to third parties. francesca's® reserves the right to make exceptions, such as when we believe that an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying or providing such information to the appropriate authorities. Also, francesca's® may share certain personal information with companies who provide certain services to us. We share only the information we believe is necessary for the performance of such services.

We retain your personal information for as long as we believe is necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.

### Cookies and an Enhanced Shopping Experience

francesca's® uses “cookies” to provide you with an enhanced website experience. A cookie is a small data file that a website sends to your browser, which is then stored on your system and collects information related to your use of this website. Some francesca's® pages use cookies so that we may better serve you when you return to our website. Cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to this website and monitor and maintain information about your visits to tailor our website to your needs.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser to disable them, but be aware that if you disable cookies, you may not have access to certain features and services that make your experience on this website more efficient and enjoyable.

### Your Communication Preferences

francesca's® offers those who sign up for our e-mail list advanced notice of sales, new merchandise, boutique openings, and other francesca's® news. E-mail addresses collected on this website are used internally and by our business partners. If you wish to unsubscribe from our e-mail list, you may use the link provided at the bottom of each francesca's® e-mail. Alternatively, you may make changes to your communication preferences through your account online or contact [Guest Services](http://www.francescas.com/category/customer+service/contact+us.do). In the event you choose to unsubscribe, we will promptly remove your e-mail address from our mailing list. Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by e-mail. We may also need to contact you via telephone, e-mail or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

### Secure Shopping

Orders placed on our website are encrypted using SSL technology, the industry-standard authentication and encryption technology, to protect transactions. In order for SSL security to work properly, you must use an SSL enabled browser. Data transmissions over the Internet or any wireless network cannot be guaranteed as completely secure, and you understand through your use of this website that certain Internet security issues are beyond our control. If you have any concerns, you may call our Guest Services line at 1.800.980.1180, Monday through Saturday, 7:00 a.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST. and Sunday, 10:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. CST.

Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting sensitive information, including credit card numbers. We will never ask for sensitive information via e-mail, and if you receive an e-mail that appears to be an e-mail from francesca's® requesting sensitive information, do not respond as this might be a scam designed to steal such information.

### Social Media

We may offer you the opportunity to engage with our content through third-party social networking websites. When you engage with our content on or through third-party websites, you allow us to have access to certain information associated with your social media account, and we may use that information to enhance your experience on our website.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website contains links to websites owned by third parties. Please review the privacy policy of any website you access through our website as we are not responsible for a third party’s privacy policy or practices. 

### Policy Changes

francesca's® may periodically update this Privacy & Security Policy and will post any changes to this website with the applicable date of revision. By visiting this website, you agree to accept any changes made to this policy. Please note that our Privacy & Security Policy is incorporated into this website’s Terms of Use.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy & Security Policy, please feel free to contact our [Guest Services](http://www.francescas.com/category/customer+service/contact+us.do) department.
